好了  维罗  准备好了么
Okay, Willow, ready?
集中注意力  向我投球  就朝着这儿
Focus. Fire one at me. Right here.
太棒了
Perfect...
如果我们是在玩砸花盆的话
If we were playing "smash that pot."
维罗  你状态几天都不好了
Willow, you've been in a slump for days.
我只是不能全神贯注罢了
I just can't concentrate.
那好  垒球选拔赛就在这周末
Okay, well, softball tryouts are this weekend,
如果我们要成为校队里的首批二年级生的话
and if we want to be the first sophomores to make varsity,
你就必须得认真投入比赛
then you gotta get your head in the game.
你到底遇上什么问题了
What is your problem?
你知道吗  我一说起这事
You know what? I just don't feel comfortable
就浑身不舒服
talking about it.
那行  我们必须要趁着选拔赛前
Okay, well, we have to get to the bottom
把你所有的问题都消灭干净
of whatever this is before tryouts.
如果你不愿意和我聊天的话
And if you're not willing to talk to me,
也许我们就需要一些专业的帮助了
then maybe we need some professional help.
谁刚刚说了专业的帮助来着
Did someone say "professional help"?
这一天终于到来了
It is finally happening.